enetget.com 2019-06-27

# eNetGet Social Network | Privacy Policy

###  Privacy Policy

We (eNetGet) are committed to protecting users' (your) privacy and make your experience in eNetGet as enjoyable as possible. What is covered in this privacy notice is very similar to other similar websites but there might be minor differences.

This privacy policy primarily covers how eNetGet uses personal information you submitted to us or that we receive from you. Personal information includes, but not limited to, your name and email address. This policy only covers eNetGet and does not represent any other companies/websites and other people such as eNetGet users.

## How do we use your personal information?

eNetGet primarily uses your personal information to customize your experience so that we can better serve you, matching your interests and needs with our products and services. We do not sell, rent or share individual personal information with other people or companies except to provide services or products to you in eNetGet, or when we have your permission to do so. We may, however, share aggregate demographic statistics about members such as interests or occupations, but advertisers and third parties can never access your individual personal information. There are, however, exceptions about providing your personal information. These exceptions include:

  * when we respond to court orders or any orders from law enforcement or judicial governmental authorities, but only upon the receipt of appropriate documentation(s);
  * when we use them to defend against legal claims or exercise our legal rights;
  * when we have to investigate or take action against illegal or suspicious activities;
  * when we believe there is a violation of eNetGet"s terms of use;
  * when there is a merger or acquisition activity between eNetGet and another company. In this case, we will notify you before your personal information is being transferred to that company. You may, however, be subjected to a different privacy policy;
  * when required by law.

## Cookies

Every time you visit eNetGet, your web browser may be assigned "cookies" that includes but not limited to, information about your IP address, specific type of browser and the pages you visited in eNetGet. Cookies alone cannot be used to find out the identity of any individual user. It can only identify your browser but not the individual user whenever you use eNetGet. Cookies are primarily used to provide convenience and customized contents to you, such as automatically signing you in every time you visit eNetGet and providing promotions that might interests you. Our uses of cookies include, but not limited to, diagnosing and fixing problems that users encountered or may encounter in the future and limiting access to those users who violated the Terms of Use of eNetGet.

## Subscribing to and Unsubscribing from Emails

Email communications can subscribed to and unsubscribed from in the following ways:

  * Click the 'Unsubscribe' link in our emails, and unsubscribe yourself from that kind of email with a single click.
  * In eNetGet, click 'My Account', which appears at the top right of every page, and from the drop down menu click 'Email Settings'. On the 'Email Settings' page, uncheck all email types that you no longer wish to receive, and click 'Save' button to register the changes.

## Editing your personal information

You can always edit your personal information by going to My eNetGet => Edit Profile. 

## Protecting your password

Please keep your password in a safe place. We strongly advise users to change their passwords frequently and not to share their accounts with anyone.

eNetGet will never ask for your password. Anyone or any company representing eNetGet asking for your password is definitely a con.

## How do we protect your personal information

We will try our best to protect your personal information but no internet traffic can be guaranteed to be 100% safe and secure. Therefore, we do not ensure or guarantee the security of any information sent or transmitted to us, and by doing so, you do so at your own risk.

## Updating the Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change the privacy notice of eNetGet anytime for any reason. We may or may not inform you in the event of updating our privacy notice.
